- Alexa, are we friends?
- Yes.
She said you haven't been sleeping.
You need your rest.
You still having them?
In this day and age,
it's sicker not having panic attacks.
Fuck!
Wow. I've never touched
something so beautiful.
I feel the same way each time.
Can't we just be a normal couple
that looks up vacation
packages to Budapest?
Just so you know...
Full-time freelance now.
Only loyalty is to the almighty paper.
I want you to destroy
Whiterose's machine.
Everything you need to know is on here.
You can't make your own currency.
That is the federal government's job.
With Ecoin equal to $1,
we are the authority.
You know that night we spent together.
So this is why you came
here. You were just using me.
You know it was more than that.
Well, I am not leaving you like this.
You wanna help me?
This is all my fault.
Take them down.
The data dump from fsociety was easily
the largest and most damning
doxxing case in history.
While only a small percentage
of the documents in the breach
have been substantiated at this time,
those that have are
proving to be accurate.
With regard to their source,
the intelligence community is cautioning
the overall veracity of the data dump
and rush to judgment, citing
fears falsified documents...
And then your 1K letter
to the FBI will be issued
by the US Attorney's office
once everything you've told us,
and what you've logged
in here, checks out.
Now, I do need to mention
these are some serious crimes
you committed, Agent DiPierro.
You may come out of this with a record.
There's not much we can do about that.
China's Minister of State
Security has been exposed
as the infamous hacker
and leader of the Dark Army
known only as Whiterose.
Intelligence officials
who have long thought
Whiterose's identity...
Those dresses he showed me.
Were the key to confirming
Zhang's double life.
He was trying to tell me who he was.
Saying it was the missing
link that finally allowed them
to connect Whiterose...
I'm sorry, who are you referring to?
China has yet to officially
respond to the claims...
Nothing.
In either the Deus
Group or the Dark Army.
As for your job at the Bureau,
you're on administrative
leave for six months
- until OPR does their thing.
- What's in the bag?
Oh. This is saline.
We'll be putting some medicine in there
- so you can get some rest.
- No.
No drugs. I don't want any drugs.
I'm gonna leave soon anyway.
Oh, sweetie, you can't
leave here anytime soon.
She's right, Dom. You need to stay put.
Plus, with everything
going on out there,
we don't think you
should go home anyway.
I'm not going home. I
need to see my family.
They're in one of our safe houses, Dom.
SO-4's watching them, 24/7 rotation.
I need to see them for myself.
Have already issued a joint
statement on the matter.
Um... that can't happen.
The heck is that supposed to mean?
They're my family. I
should be able to see them.
It's like I said.
Until OPR clears you...
I'm not cleared?
World Bank, WTO, and
the US Federal Reserve
are still trying to
piece together the events.
Reports continue to come
in from around the globe
of the far reaching cyber heist.
I can't believe this.
The confirmed victims of the robbery
include prominent businessmen, CEOs...
You don't trust me to know
where my own family is?
Not now, no.
Officials believe the
compromised Deus Group
accounts were managed
by Cyprus National Bank.
They're thought to be at
the center of the hack.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
All you need to worry about right now
is getting a good night's sleep.
This hospital's gonna
take great care of you.
Now make sure she gets
whatever she needs.
Deus Group lost trillions
of dollars in cyber-attacks.
Law enforcement
authorities suspect fsociety
to be the architects of the heist...
Can I get you anything before I go?
I wanna go home.
Pardon me?
I have to go home.
Sweetheart, it's like I said earlier,
the doctor isn't recommend...
The doctor said the surgery went great.
Right?
And I'm able to walk around just fine
as long as I don't tear my stitches.
You can't legally keep
me here if I wanna leave.
Yes, we can discharge you
against medical advice, but...
That's what I want.
I really appreciate this, but
I don't need this wheelchair.
Hospital policy, ma'am.
Did the nurse call your pickup contact?
What?
Who's picking you up?
Nobody's picking me up.
What's that?
Just gonna grab a cab.
You can't do that, ma'am.
Why not?
Since the hospital
administered anesthesia,
you have to have somebody with you.
Can't just put you in
a cab with a stranger.
You sure there's nobody you can call?
A friend, a family member...
No.
I don't have anyone.
What about one of those FBI
guys that was here earlier?
I could give one of them a call.
Definitely not.
All right.
I'm gonna check the Social
Services volunteer list
and see who we have available today.
It'll just take a sec.
Hang tight. I'll be back.
This is ridiculous... I told
you, I'm good, I'm just gonna...
Can I trust you to behave?
Or do we need to bring
security over here?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Open up. We don't have a lot of time.
What the fuck is going on here?
Don't worry about
that. We're not staying.
You shouldn't even be here.
When I...
It took me forever to find
what hospital you were at,
and when I found out you went home...
Want a grilled cheese sandwich?
Why are you even here?
Shouldn't you still be at the hospital?
Probably.
Figured not the safest place to be,
given what you guys did.
Saw the news, guess you
really pulled it off.
Which is why we need to
get the fuck out of here.
Elliot and I have a
getaway plan lined up,
and I think it'd be in your
best interest to come with us.
I'm not going anywhere.
Dom, you cannot stay here.
Best bet is to leave with us
until this whole thing blows over.
I have to stay here
until the OPR investigation
clears my name.
Who gives a shit about that?
I do.
Why?
Because then I can see my family again.
Then I can finally apologize to them
for everything I put them through.
Alexa, play some Faith Hill.
Shuffling songs by Faith Hill.
I can't remember the last time
I had a good grilled cheese sandwich.
Every day, I'd come home from work
and say I was gonna make myself
a grilled cheese sandwich,
but I was always too tired.
♪ Baby hello, oh no, Good-bye ♪
Now I've finally done it.
♪ Shooting straight across the sky ♪
♪ It's the way you love me ♪
You want a bite?
So that's it then? You're just gonna
sit here and wait for the
Dark Army to come kill you?
Or did you actually think
that dresser over there
was gonna do anything more
than throw off your feng shui?
I told you, I need to stay here.
What you need is to hit the road with me
and get a good night's
sleep somewhere safe.
You know, you're the second person
that's told me that today.
Good night's sleep.
Boss said the same thing.
♪ All I wanted was a white knight ♪
Five years.
I haven't really slept in five years,
save for a few nightmares.
Not true. Saw you sleeping
last time I was here.
You mean when I busted you
stealing my badge out of my safe?
♪ It's centrifugal motion ♪
Yeah, I wasn't really
asleep then either.
♪ It's that pivotal moment ♪
♪ It's unthinkable ♪
♪ This kiss, this kiss ♪
♪ Unsinkable ♪
What are you doing?
Where do you keep your socks?
Darlene.
Stop!
You're coming with me.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
Well, I'm not gonna let you
just sit here and wait to die.
As opposed to what you're doing?
What's your plan, anyway? Run?
How long? How far?
Where is this magical place
when you're gonna feel safe enough
to stop looking over your shoulder?
I'm not gonna let the Dark Army
kill another person I care about.
Not when there's something
I can still do about it.
I'm good, Darlene. The FBI has my back.
The FBI has you under investigation.
♪ Subliminal ♪
♪ This kiss, this kiss ♪
♪ It's criminal ♪
Fine. You want my underwear, go for it.
Dom, we have a plan. A good one.
We've got fake passports, plane
tickets, and safe transport.
Just come with me.
♪ It's the way you love me ♪
You're just gonna sit there all alone.
I'm not alone.
I have Alexa, remember?
Sorry, I'm having trouble
understanding right now.
Ugh!
The fuck did you just do?
Snap the fuck out of it!
This is not a person!
She is not real. She is not your friend.
She is just a robot you
use to buy paper towels.
Look around you. Dom, this is emptiness.
There is nothing here for you,
but there is still a
chance for you out there
if you come with us.
Now go get your toothbrush.
Why don't you go ahead without me?
I'll be there in a few minutes.
Looks like you found her okay.
Yeah, she's...
still a little shell-shocked,
but she'll be fine.
How about you?
You're not...
gonna come with us, are you?
I need to go back to Washington Township
and you cannot come with me this time.
I don't want to.
This was it for me.
I'm done now.
Before I go...
You wanna do the honors?
All the money has been passed
through multiple crypto
tumblers and shell accounts.
Should be completely untraceable now.
It's ready to go out.
This should be you.
This is your win, not mine.
Are you sure you don't
want to come with us?
I can't. I'm not done.
Well, in that case, any
advice for a road trip?
I've never been on one before.
Neither have I.
Recommend getting a
bunch of Sour Patch Kids.
For you to play with.
I wish we were there now.
Well, it's a long way yet.
Past the great rock that
looks like a Long Neck.
Oh, hey.
Still a long way, but we'll get there.
Holy shit.
I'm sorry, have we met?
Yes, we fucking met.
The barn?
Doesn't ring a bell.
You shot four people?
Hey Hopper, come back!
Oh, shit! That's right!
Now I've got you.
You again? Go away!
What the hell is going on?
You're Dark Army.
No, dude.
I'm actually here to help
my boy Elliot and his sis.
So what, you're just a...
a gun for hire, or...
I mean, it's like I always say:
Gotta keep a open mind
at every opportunity
that comes your way.
You've seen that one movie,
"Three Days of the Condor," right?
Dude, you've never seen
"Three Days of the Condor,"
and you're a fucking FBI agent?
You've gotta check that out.
Normally I don't go for
that '70s paranoia shit,
but I don't know, this one...
this one really spoke to me.
You know, maybe it was
what my boy Joubert says:
"I don't interest myself in the why.
I think more often
in terms of the when,
sometimes where, but always how much."
I fucking felt that.
Got me opening up my eyes
to diversifying my revenue
streams and whatnot.
Yo, last quarter, I nearly
tripled my net profits,
according to this
chick who does my books,
and shorty Japanese,
so you know she know what
the fuck she talking about.
She got me stumped off
this one question, though,
saying that I should incorporate sooner.
What do you think? S Corp, or LLC?
Oh, shit.
I forgot to tell you
he's working with us now.
You should get some rest.
So I've heard.
♪ Midnight hour ♪
♪ Almost over ♪
It's pretty out here.
I've never driven to Boston this way.
We're taking the scenic route.
♪ One more chance couldn't be... ♪
Yeah, believe it or not,
Connecticut's swarming with Dark Army,
given the concentration of RWAs.
Rich, white assholes.
Yep, that's who they like
doing their business with.
Usually, that's their
number one client, in fact.
Anyways, that's why we're
staying off the main roads.
Besides, I gotta find
a rest stop anyway.
Gotta steal me a mirror real quick.
♪ I wonder what you'll do ♪
♪ When your chance rolls around ♪
What, do you not know your Vonnegut?
♪ You gotta know how
much I want to keep you ♪
I gotta take a whiz, okay?
Too many Code Reds this morning.
♪ I'm afraid it will all fall down ♪
Man, nobody fucking reads anymore.
♪ Wait for me, all right ♪
♪ I guess that's more than I should ask ♪
♪ But won't you wait for me ♪
♪ Please wait for me ♪
♪ Although I know the
light is fading fast ♪
What do you think of Jackie?
Jackie's whoever you want her to be.
Yeah, it's easy for you to say.
You're not pretending
to be someone you're not.
You think Leon's my real name?
♪ And ours is doing nothing ♪
♪ But all the time we spent ♪
♪ It must be good for something ♪
♪ Please forgive all the
disturbance I'm creating ♪
♪ But you got a lot to learn
if you think I'm not... ♪
Where are we?
In the land of RWAs.
♪ Wait for me, oh, I ♪
Best you keep your eye out.
Jackie's a diehard for Hall & Oates.
She's a gym teacher.
No, she's not a gym teacher. She's a...
pastry chef.
She's got a soft spot for Nutella.
We ready?
Not yet. Leon said something
about stealing a mirror
and then went on about
how illiterate America is
and then said he had
to piss a bunch of red,
so I took that as my cue to walk away.
Look at all these people.
They're all probably
on their way back home.
Holidays are over.
It's back to the grind
for most of them, I guess.
It sucks.
I wanna show you something. Come on.
Should we really be out
in the open like this?
I don't know.
Maybe not, but...
For once, I wanna drop the paranoia
and just take all this in.
Just for this moment.
What is this moment, exactly?
Watch this.
What did you just do?
Just give it a few seconds.
Darlene, you're worrying me.
I'm pretty good at that, aren't I?
- Tell me.
- Be patient.
- If you did something, I need to know.
- Oh, do you?
Is this something illegal again?
- Dom.
- I'm serious, Darlene.
- If you don't tell me what you're up to...
- Just wait.
What is it with you
and breaking the law?
It's like a fetish.
Shut the fuck up and just watch.
I don't get it.
What's going on?
All of the money
Whiterose and her cronies
have been stealing for decades
just went back to the people.
How?
We found a way to evenly
disperse it anonymously
into everyone's Ecoin wallets.
Everyone got this much?
Yep.
And due to E Corp's insistence
that Ecoin remain independent
from the US dollar,
it is completely impossible
for them to reverse the transactions.
This is illegal. This is stealing.
After what the Dark Army did to you?
Fuck, after what they did to everyone,
you really wanna start defending them?
This isn't what justice
is supposed to look like.
We have laws for a reason.
And they were so powerful,
they wrote the laws
to benefit themselves.
They got away with everything
because they banked on us,
all of us, to trust the system.
That was our vulnerability,
and they took advantage of it.
It took this to finally stop them,
and you were a part of it.
Look around.
This is it.
Everything we've been through
led up to this one moment...
The greatest redistribution
of wealth in history.
We just Robin Hooded
those evil motherfuckers.
If you ask me, this is exactly
what justice looks like.
Whoo!
People are staring at you.
I don't care!
Fuck yeah, bitches!
May I have your attention, please.
This area is for loading
and unloading only.
Vehicles must be attended at all times.
For security reasons...
Hey, make sure you check
out that Sydney Pollack joint
when you get a chance.
Thank me later, Jackie.
So...
Did you keep any of it?
Keep what?
Covert. That's cool.
I'm saying, though,
if you're looking to get into
some shit when you get back,
I got some shit for you.
Like what?
Adventures and whatnot.
You know, a high like this...
it don't come so easy with the normies.
Thanks, dude, but, uh,
I'm trying to lay low for a bit.
No doubt.
But with skills like
yours, the pay is good,
and you get to be your
own boss, 'cause you know,
you a boss, girl.
Let me think about it.
Cool.
Till the next episode, then.
Vehicles must be attended at all times.
For security reasons,
unattended vehicles...
You should not accept offers
of transportation from anyone
without prior arrangement.
Dom?
How the hell are you?
Hey, you coming over
here to pick up a copy?
Hey, they're great for long flights.
A real page turner,
especially when you get to the part
where he strangles his
mother to death in Chapter 12.
Spoiler alert!
You know, today's your lucky day.
I'm gonna sign you a copy.
Here you go.
Aw, come on.
Yeah, the book's flying off the shelves.
It's a real stocking stuffer.
In fact, that's what I'm doing here.
I got a little book tour stop at UMass.
Anyway, how have you been?
Is that Elliot's sister?
You two a thing now, or...
I knew I picked up on something.
Please don't hurt us.
Hurt you?
Why would I hurt you?
Because I...
I disobeyed orders,
I... I killed my handler.
Oh, she was a pain in the ass.
Trust me, you were doing them a favor.
And... and your little
loudmouth friend over there,
yeah, well, what she did
was a bad thing, but...
Well, word around camp is
they don't care about you two no more.
What do you mean?
They've picked up and skedaddled off
to something more important.
Where?
That I can't tell you.
But all those things you said
you were gonna do to my family.
No one cares about your family now.
Look, I'm telling you, the
Dark Army's not something
you need to worry about anymore.
Look, if they wanted to get to you two,
I would know about it.
Trust me.
But... But I...
I saw you butcher Santiago with
an axe when he got out of line.
Yeah.
That was fun.
All right, well,
this was nice.
I'm gonna go.
Make sure you pay for that.
She still needs to pay for that.
Take it easy, Dom.
Just wanted me to buy one of his books.
And you did?
The cashier made me
because he autographed it.
He actually said they
don't care anymore.
Yep.
I don't get it.
Where did the Dark Army go?
I don't know, he wouldn't tell me.
All I know is we don't
have to run anymore.
Yeah, but we're here.
Might as well still go.
I've heard Budapest is pretty dope.
Why Budapest anyway?
Cisco always talked about going there,
but once what happened, happened
I just couldn't go by myself.
Globe Airlines flight 4057 to Budapest
will begin boarding at Gate B31.
That's us. We should get going.
Where's your brother?
He's not coming with us.
Why not?
He's running behind.
He's gonna catch the next flight out.
Let's go.
Wait.
I can't do this.
Can't do what?
You convinced me to come
because the Dark Army was a threat.
Now they're not.
Doesn't mean we still can't go.
Do you even really want
to go to Budapest anyway?
You said it yourself, this
was Cisco's dream, not yours.
Then, we won't go there.
When we land, we'll hitch
a ride to somewhere else.
Just come with me.
Darlene.
I can't go.
♪ In these lines ♪
♪ I know you're looking forward to them ♪
But you said you would.
♪ What is it that has my mind ♪
You don't need me to come with you.
Whatever your brother's actually up to,
you don't need him, either.
No, I can't handle shit
solo, Dom. You've seen me.
I get panic attacks, I freak out...
You're gonna be fine.
I'm no good on my own.
I've tried.
♪ And their colors create my mood ♪
I'm sorry.
♪ Two places I've never been ♪
I've got responsibilities
here, I can't just...
walk away from my family, my job, my...
Responsibilities? That's
what this is about?
You know your family is
safe. Your job is on hold.
There is nothing for you to do here.
Jesus, Dom, no wonder you can't sleep.
You hold on to a lot, and
you hold on fucking tight.
Maybe running away
might actually help you.
Running away to Budapest will help me?
This isn't about Budapest.
You leave this airport,
you're just gonna go back to
the grind like everyone else.
I'm talking about
giving yourself a break.
Okay? About finally letting go.
Global Airlines flight 4057 to Budapest
will begin boarding at Gate B31.
Send me a postcard, okay?
One other thing.
I wrote down the number
of a friend of mine.
He works at US Cyber Command.
Your bright idea is
for me to be some pig?
When you're ready to grow up.
Don't take too long, though.
They need you.
They can't handle me.
Welcome, ladies and gentleman,
to Global Airlines
flight 4057 to Budapest.
Boarding will begin shortly.
First we would like to
invite any passengers
that need extra time or assistance...
you now will come
aboard through gate B31.
We are now boarding all passengers
in group A and group B.
Ladies and gentleman,
group C, you are welcome
to board for flight 4057.
Excuse me, are you okay?
Everyone, please take your seats
and fasten your seatbelts.
We will be closing
the cabin doors shortly
in preparation for takeoff.
Ma'am?
Are you okay? Is there
something I can help you with?
Are you missing something?
No, I'm good.
Do you need any help?
No.
No, thanks, I'm okay.
Final call for flight 4057 to Budapest.
That your flight they just called?
Yeah.
Yeah, but I'm not going.
Are you sure? I can get someone.
No.
No, I've got it.
I can take care of myself.
Have your seat backs in an
upright position for takeoff.
Thank you.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net